Preliminary Guide to the I. Richard Savage Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
I. Richard Savage papers
1951-1995
MS 1608
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
27.25
(24 boxes)
The papers consist of correspondence, topical and project files, teaching materials, and writings which document I. Richard Savage's career as a statistician and professor of statistics. Also included are three volumes of autobiographical essays.
Savage, I. Richard
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of I. Richard Savage, 1991 and 1995.
Biographical / Historical
I. Richard Savage was born in Detroit, Michigan on October 26, 1925. He received his bachelor's degree from the University of Chicago in 1944, a master's degree from the University of Michigan in 1945, and a doctoral degree from Columbia University in 1954.
Savage was a specialist in population censuses and surveys, among other topics, Professor Savage in recent years has focused his research on the role of mathematical applications in the undergraduate mathematics curriculum, statistics for allocations of funds, modifying census counts, problems associated with ability testing of handicapped people and social statistical systems. Savage was a statistician at the National Bureau of Standards from 1951-1954, and an acting assistant professor of statistics at Stanford University from 1954-1957 and he was also a visiting professor at Harvard Business School and the Imperial College of London. He was a faculty member at the University of Minnesota from 1957-1963, and was a professor at Florida State University from 1963-1974. Savage joined the Yale University faculty in 1974 as a professor of statistics, a position he held until his retirement in 1991. He has been a fellow of the American Statistical Association and the Institute of Mathematical Statistics, a member of the International Statistical Institute, and editor of the Journal of the American Statistical Association and of Annals of Statistics.
He served from 1972 to 1980 on National Research Council committees and served as president of the American Statistical Association in 1984.
Scope and Contents
The papers consist of correspondence, topical and project files, teaching materials, and writings which document I. Richard Savage's career as a statistician and professor of statistics. Also included are three volumes of autobiographical essays.
Statistics -- Study and teaching; Savage, I. Richard; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University. Dept. of Statistics
- Series I, 1955-1989; 27 linear feet (23 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Preliminary inventory by Carol King and Kate Lewis 1991 Jul
  Received from: I. Richard Savage, 1991 June 14
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - A (Box 1)
    - Aberle, David F. (Box 1)
    - Abruzzi, Adam (Box 1)
    - ABT Associates, Inc. (Box 1)
    - Accessibility (Box 1)
    - Adams, Tom (Box 1)
    - Adelman, Irma (Box 1)
    - Adler, Leta M. (Box 1)
    - Administrative Sciences: undergraduate program (Box 1)
    - Advisory Task Force on Statistical Education (Box 1)
    - Afifi, A. A., Elashoff, R. M., and Langley, P. L. (Box 1)
    - Ager, J. W. Jr., and Brent, Sander B. (Box 1)
    - Agha, M. (Box 1)
    - Ahmad, Ibrahim A. (Box 1)
    - Ahmad, Munir (Box 1)
    - Ahsanullah, Mohammed (Box 1)
    - Ahuja, J. C. (Box 1)
    - Air Pollution Control Association: "Field Tests Show Gasoline Deposit Control Additives Effective in Emission Reduction" (Box 1)
    - Alam, Khursheed (Box 1)
    - Alessi George Holly (Box 1)
    - Allen, David M. (Box 1)
    - Alling, David W. (Box 1)
    - Allyn and Bacon, Inc. (Box 1)
    - Almond, G. (Box 1)
    - American Mathematical Society (Box 1)
    - American Political Science Review (Box 1)
    - American Society for Quality Control (Box 1)
    - American Sociological Review (Box 1)
    - American Statistical Association
      General note
      See also: box 3
      - General - List of Fellows (Box 1)
      - Committee on Committees (Box 1)
    - Ames, R. C., and Higgins, A. C. (Box 1)
    - Ammann, Larry (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Donald A. (Box 1)
    - Andersen, J. T. (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Kenneth E., and Barnhart, E. L. (Box 1)
    - Anderson, R. L. (Box 1)
    - Anderson, T. W. (Box 1)
    - Andrews, D. F. (Box 1)
    - Annals of Mathematical Statistics: associate editorship (Box 1)
    - Anscombe, Frank (Box 1)
    - Antelman, Gordon (Box 1)
    - Appleton-Century-Crofts (Box 1)
    - Arden House (Box 1)
    - Argabright, Loren (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Barry C. (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Jesse C. (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Jonathan (Box 1)
    - Aroian, Leo A. (Box 1)
    - Arrow, Kenneth J. (Box 1)
    - Askovitz, S. I. (Box 1)
    - Assembly of Behavioral and Social Sciences. Executive Committee of National Research Council (Box 1)
    - Atiqullah, M. (Box 1)
    - Atkinson, G. F. (Box 1)
    - Attneave, Fred (Box 1)
    - Auerbach, Oscar, and Hammond, E. Cuyler (Box 1)
    - B (Box 1)
    - Bahadur, R. R. (Box 2)
    - Bailar, Barbara (Box 2)
    - Bainbridge, J. R. (Box 2)
    - Baker, G. A. (Box 2)
    - Baldwin. Roger R. (Box 2)
    - Banks, David L. (Box 2)
    - Barlow, Richard E. (Box 2)
    - Barndorff-Nielsen, Ole (Box 2)
    - Barron, Bruce A. (Box 2)
    - Bartholomew, David J. (Box 2)
    - Bartos, Otomar J. (Box 2)
    - Basu, Asit P. (Box 2)
    - Bayes, Thomas (Box 2)
    - Beakley, Guy W. (Box 2)
    - Beaman, Jacob E. (Box 2)
    - Beauchamp, John Jones (Box 2)
    - Bechhofer, Robert (Box 2)
    - Behboodian, Javad (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Bell, Charles B. (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Belz, Maurice (Box 2)
    - Benard, A. (Box 2)
    - Bennett, J. F. (Box 2)
    - Benton, Diane (Box 2)
    - Bergman, Sten (Box 2)
    - Bergstrom, Harald (Box 2)
    - Berk, Robert H. (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Berkson, Joseph (Box 2)
    - Berkun, Mitchell M. (Box 2)
    - Berlyne, Daniel E. (Box 2)
    - Berman, Simeon M. (Box 2)
    - Berndt, Gerald D. (Box 2)
    - Bertell, Rosalie (Box 2)
    - Beshers, James M. (Box 2)
    - Bhapkar, V. P. (Box 2)
    - Bhargava, Raghunandan Prasad (Box 2)
    - Bhat, B. R. (Box 2)
    - Bhat and Gani (Box 2)
    - Bhat, U. N. (Box 2)
    - Bhattacharyya, G. K.(3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Bickel, Peter (Box 2)
    - Bickerstaff, T. A. (Box 2)
    - Bilikam, J. E. (Box 2)
    - Billingsley, Patrick (Box 2)
    - Binder, Arnold (Box 2)
    - Binns, M. R. (Box 2)
    - Birnbaum, Allan (4 folders) (Box 2)
    - Birnbaum and Laska (Box 2)
    - Birnbaum, Z. W. (Box 2)
    - Blackman, Nelson (Box 2)
    - Blackwell, David (Box 2)
    - Blaisdell Publishing Company (Box 2)
    - Blau, Peter M. (Box 2)
    - Blischke, Wallace R. Truelove, A. J., and Mundle, P. B. (Box 2)
    - Block, Albert B. (Box 2)
    - Blom, Gunnar (Box 2)
    - Blomquist, Mary M. (Box 2)
    - Blot, Bill (Box 2)
    - Blumen, Isadore (Box 2)
    - Blumenthal, Saul (Box 2)
    - Blumke, Charles Frederick (Box 2)
    - Bodo, Erwin Peter (Box 2)
    - Bofinger, Eve (Box 2)
    - Bolton, Gaylor M. (Box 2)
    - Book notes (Box 2)
    - Book reviews (Box 2)
    - Bose, Raj Chandra (Box 2)
    - Bowden, David C. (Box 2)
    - Bowker, Albert H. (Box 2)
    - Bowren, P. W. (Box 2)
    - Box, George E. P. (4 folders) (Box 2)
    - Brackman, Rita (Box 2)
    - Bradley, James V. (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Bradley, Ralph (Box 2)
    - Braga-Illa, Alvise A. (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Breakwell, John V. (Box 2)
    - Brenna, Leroy Stanley, and Kramer, Clyde Young (Box 2)
    - Breslow, Norman (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Breuer, Joseph (Box 2)
    - Brewer, James Kenneth (Box 2)
    - Brewer, K. R. W., Carroll, J. L., and Hanif, M. (Box 2)
    - Brock, Samuel (Box 2)
    - Broemeling, L. D. (Box 2)
    - Bronfenbrenner, Urie (Box 2)
    - Brooks, Samuel H. (Box 2)
    - Brosin (Box 2)
    - Brown, Byron (Box 2)
    - Brown, Earl D. (Box 2)
    - Brown, Morton B., and Forsythe, Alan (Box 2)
    - Brown University (Box 2)
    - Brownlee, Oswald H. (Box 2)
    - Bryson, Marion (Box 2)
    - Bryson, Maurice C., and Siddiqui, M. M. (Box 2)
    - Buehler, Robert J. (Box 2)
    - Bulgren, W. G. (Box 2)
    - Burke, Peter J. (Box 2)
    - Burkholder, Donald L. (Box 2)
    - Burnett, Thomas D. (Box 2)
    - Burr, Irving (Box 2)
    - Burros, Raymond H. (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - Bury, Karl, and Bernhotz, B. (Box 2)
    - Butler, Frank E., Jr. (Box 2)
    - Buttrick, John A. (Box 2)
    - Byhre, Otto V., Jr. (Box 2)
    - C (Box 2)
    - Calcutta (International Symposium on Recent Trends of Research in Statistics. Indian Statistical Institute) (Box 3)
    - Cameron, Joseph (Box 3)
    - Cancian, Frank (Box 3)
    - Canner, Paul L. (Box 3)
    - Capobianco, Michael F. (Box 3)
    - Cardinal Management Corporation (Box 3)
    - Carruccio, Ettore (Box 3)
    - Caspari, Ernst Wolfgang (Box 3)
    - Catastrophe theory (Box 3)
    - Census Seminar (National Research Council. Division of Behavioral Sciences) (Box 3)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 3)
    - Carnea, Michael (Box 3)
    - Chadwick, Richard W. (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Chairman: miscellaneous(?) (Box 3)
    - Chalmers, E. Larry (Box 3)
    - Champion, John (Box 3)
    - Chan, Lai K. (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Chan, M. W. (Box 3)
    - Chanda, Kamal C. (Box 3)
    - Chapin, Ned (Box 3)
    - Chaan, J. B. (Box 3)
    - Chatterjee (?) (Box 3)
    - Chatterjee, Shubhra (Box 3)
    - Cheng, M. C. (Box 3)
    - Chernoff, Herman (Box 3)
    - Childers, Grant W., Mayhew, Bruce H., Jr., and Gray, Louis N. (Box 3)
    - Chin, Long Chiang/Dr. Chiang (Box 3)
    - Chipman, John S. (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - chitgopekar, Sharad S. (Box 3)
    - Choi, S. C. (Box 3)
    - Choudary, Hanumara (Box 3)
    - Chow, Gregory C. (Box 3)
    - Christ, Carl F. (Box 3)
    - Chu, J. T. (Box 3)
    - Civil Service Department (Box 3)
    - Clark, Robert E. (Box 3)
    - [Clelland?] (Box 3)
    - Clickner, Robert (Box 3)
    - Clutton-Brock, M. (Box 3)
    - Coale, Ansley J. (Box 3)
    - Cochran, William G. (Box 3)
    - Cohen, A. Clifford (Box 3)
    - Cohn, Harvey (Box 3)
    - Collier, Raymond O. (Box 3)
    - Comer, John P., Jr. (Box 3)
    - Committee for the Evaluation of Teaching Effectiveness (Box 3)
    - Committee of Presidents of Statistical Societies (COPSS). American Statistical Association (Box 3)
    - Committee on Committees: U.S. Department of Commerce. Bureau of the Census (Box 3)
    - Committee on National Statistics (Box 3)
    - Committee on Promotions and Tenure. Florida State University. Department of Statistics (Box 3)
    - Committee on Search for Chairman of Applied Mathematics Department. Florida State University (Box 3)
    - Comstock, R. E. (Box 3)
    - Conlon, Barbara Anne (Box 3)
    - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering (Box 3)
    - Connor, Robert J. (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Connor, William S. (Box 3)
    - Conover, W. J. (Box 3)
    - Conroy, John (Box 3)
    - Consulting (Box 3)
    - Conviser, Richard H. (Box 3)
    - Coombs, Robert H. (Box 3)
    - Copas, John B. (Box 3)
    - Cornell, John A., and Good, I. J. (Box 3)
    - Cornell, Richard G. (Box 3)
    - Cornfield, Jerome (Box 3)
    - Corps of Engineers (U. S. Army Corps of Engineers) (Box 3)
    - Cotton, John W., and Jahnke, J. C. (Box 3)
    - Courtney, Wayne (Box 3)
    - Cowden, Dudley J. (Box 3)
    - Crawford, Bryce, Jr. (Box 3)
    - Crow, Larry Hart (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Cruickshank (?) (Box 3)
    - Cureton, Edward E. (Box 3)
    - D (Box 4)
    - D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc. (Box 4)
    - Dagenais, Marcel G. (Box 4)
    - D'Agostino, Ralph B. (Box 4)
    - Dagum, Camilio (Box 4)
    - Dalenius, Tore (Box 4)
    - Daniel, Cuthbert (Box 4)
    - David, F. N. (Box 4)
    - David, Herbert A. (Box 4)
    - Davidson, Roger (Box 4)
    - Davies, Vernon (Box 4)
    - Deely, John J., Amos, D. E., and Steck, G. P. (Box 4)
    - DeGroot, Morris (Box 4)
    - Deming, W. Edwards and Lola S. (Box 4)
    - Demography (Box 4)
    - Dempster, Arthur P. (Box 4)
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 4)
    - Department of Statistics. Florida State University: minutes, notices, memoranda (Box 4)
    - Derman, Cyrus (Box 4)
    - DeRobertis, Lorraine (Box 4)
    - Deshpande, Jayant V. (Box 4)
    - De Solla Price, Derek (Box 4)
    - Deutsch, Karl W. (Box 4)
    - Dickey, James M. (Box 4)
    - Disabled Student Program. Florida State University (Box 4)
    - Distinguished Professor Selection Committee. Florida State University (Box 4)
    - Dittmer, Karl (Box 4)
    - Dixon, W. J. (Box 4)
    - Dodd, Stuart C. (Box 4)
    - Dodds, D. J., and Fryer, J. G. (Box 4)
    - Doksum, Kjell (Box 4)
    - Donahue, James (Box 4)
    - Draper, Brian (Box 4)
    - Draper, Jean E. (Box 4)
    - Drenick, R. F., and Spaulding, S. W. (Box 4)
    - Dubins, Lester (Box 4)
    - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 4)
    - Dudewicz, Edward J. (Box 4)
    - Duncan, Acheson J. (Box 4)
    - Duncan, Joseph W. (Box 4)
    - Dunn, James E. (Box 4)
    - Dunnett, Charles W. (Box 4)
    - Duran, Benjamin J., and Mielke, Paul W., Jr. (Box 4)
    - Durand, David (Box 4)
    - Dutton, Orin F. (Box 4)
    - Dwass, Meyer (Box 4)
    - Dwivedi, T. D. (Box 4)
    - E (Box 4)
    - Easterling, Robert G., and Weeks, David L. (Box 4)
    - Ebrahimi, Aziz Nosrat (Box 4)
    - Eckler, A. Ross (Box 4)
    - Ederer, Fred (Box 4)
    - Efron, Bradley (Box 4)
    - Ehrlich, Annette (Box 4)
    - Eisenberger, Isadore (Box 4)
    - Eisenhart, Churchill (Box 4)
    - Eiswirth, Richard (Box 4)
    - Ekblom, Hakan (Box 4)
    - Eklund, Darrel L., and Waller, Ray A. (Box 4)
    - Elandt-Johnson, Regina C. (Box 4)
    - El Helbawy, Abd Alla (Box 4)
    - Elkins, Thomas A. (Box 4)
    - El Neweihi, Emad Eldin A.W. (Box 4)
    - Engelman, Laszlo, and Hartigan, J. A. (Box 4)
    - Enis, Peter, and Geisser, Seymour (Box 4)
    - Epstein, Benjamin (Box 4)
    - Ericson, William A. (Box 4)
    - Esary, J. D. and Proschan, F. (Box 4)
    - F (Box 4)
    - Fairweather, David W. (Box 4)
    - Farley, John U., and Hinich, Melvin J. (Box 4)
    - Farrell, E. (Box 4)
    - Feder, Paul (Box 4)
    - Feinleib, Manning (Box 4)
    - Feinstein, Alvin R. (Box 4)
    - Feller, William (Box 4)
    - Ferber, Robert (Box 4)
    - Fienberg, Stephen E. (Box 4)
    - Fishburn, Peter (Box 4)
    - Fishelson, Gideon (Box 4)
    - Fisher, Franklin M. (Box 4)
    - Fisher, Ronald A. (Box 4)
    - Fox, Martin (Box 4)
    - Francis, Richard L. (Box 4)
    - Franken, Peter (Box 4)
    - Franklin, D. (Box 4)
    - Fraser, Donald A. S. (Box 4)
    - Freimer, Marshall (Box 4)
    - Freudenthal, A. M., and Gumbel, E. J. (Box 4)
    - Freund, Richard A., Howe, William G., and Jackson, J. Edward (Box 4)
    - Fridshal, Donald, and Posten, Harry O. (Box 4)
    - Fristedt Bert E. (Box 4)
    - Fryer. J. G. (Box 4)
    - Fuller, Wayne A., and Johnson, Nancy R. (Box 4)
    - G (Box 5)
    - Gabriel, K. R., and Feder, Paul (Box 5)
    - Gani, Joseph (Box 5)
    - Garen, Allen (Box 5)
    - Garg, R. C., and Pillai, S. S. (Box 5)
    - Garner, Norman R. (Box 5)
    - Gastwirth, Joseph L. (Box 5)
    - Gates, C. R., Charles E., N. F. W. (Box 5)
    - Gather, Ursula (Box 5)
    - Gaver, Donald P., Jr. (Box 5)
    - Gaylor, David W. (Box 5)
    - Geary, R. C. (Box 5)
    - Gebert, James R. (Box 5)
    - Gebhardt, Friedrich (Box 5)
    - Genensky, Samuel M. (Box 5)
    - Geertsema, Jan C. (Box 5)
    - Geoffrion, Arthur M. (Box 5)
    - Ghosh, B. K. (Box 5)
    - Ghurye, Sudhish G. (Box 5)
    - Gilbert, John P. (Box 5)
    - Gilliland, Dennis C., and Hansen, Eldon R. (Box 5)
    - Gillispie, Charles Coulton (Box 5)
    - Girl, N. C. (Box 5)
    - Glasser, Gerald J. (Box 5)
    - Gleason, (?) (Box 5)
    - Gleser, Leon (Box 5)
    - Glueck, Bernard, Jr. (Box 5)
    - Godambe, V. P. (Box 5)
    - Godwin, H. J. (Box 5)
    - Goldberg, Merrill B. (Box 5)
    - Goldman, Aaron S., and Zeigler, R. K. (Box 5)
    - Golhar, M. B. (Box 5)
    - Golub, Abraham, and Grubbs, Frank E. (Box 5)
    - Good, I. J. (Box 5)
    - Goodman, Irwin F. (Box 5)
    - Goodman, Leo A. (Box 5)
    - Goodman, (?), and Grunfield, (?) (Box 5)
    - Gordon, Myron J., and Taylor, William J. (Box 5)
    - Goslin, David A. (Box 5)
    - Gottinger, Hans W. (Box 5)
    - Govindarajulu, Zakkula (Box 5)
    - Grab, Edwin L., and Savage, I. R. (Box 5)
    - Graduate Policy Council Committee. Florida State University (Box 5)
    - Graybill, Franklin A., and Milliken, George A. (Box 5)
    - Green, Robert A. (Box 5)
    - Greenberg, Bernard G. (Box 5)
    - Greenberg, Irwin (Box 5)
    - Greenhut, M. L. (Box 5)
    - Greenwood, Joseph A. (Box 5)
    - Gregory, Gavin (Box 5)
    - Gridgeman, N. T. (Box 5)
    - Grigg, Charles (Box 5)
    - Grimme, Glen (Box 5)
    - Guenther, William C. (Box 5)
    - Guetzhow, H. (Box 5)
    - Gullen, W. H. (Box 5)
    - Gumbel, (?), Carlson, (?), and Mustafi, (?) (Box 5)
    - Gupta, B. N. (Box 5)
    - Guthrie, Donald, Jr., and Johns, M. V., Jr. (Box 5)
    - H (Box 5)
    - Haas, Gerald, Bain, Lee J., Dumonceaux, Robert, and Antle, Charles E. (Box 5)
    - Haberman, Shelby (Box 5)
    - Haberman, Sol (Box 5)
    - Hager, Harold W., and Bain, Lee J. (Box 5)
    - Hahn, Gerald J. (Box 5)
    - Haitovsky, Yoel (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Hajek, Jaroslav (Box 5)
    - Halberg, Franz (Box 5)
    - Halevi, Hai (Box 5)
    - Hall, I. J. (Box 5)
    - Hall, William Jackson (Box 5)
    - Halperin, Max (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Halsey, A. H. (Box 5)
    - Hamaker, H. C. (Box 5)
    - Hamburg, David A. (Box 5)
    - Hameed, Abd-El (Box 6)
    - Hammer, Carl, and Ikle, Fred (Box 6)
    - Hanson, Morgan A. (Box 6)
    - Hanson, Robert C. (Box 6)
    - Harp, Rollie (Box 6)
    - Harper and Row, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Harris, Bernard (Box 6)
    - Harris, Edward E. (Box 6)
    - Harshbarger, Boyd (Box 6)
    - Harter, H. Leon (Box 6)
    - Hartigan, J. (Box 6)
    - Hartigan, J. A. (Box 6)
    - Hartley, H. O. (Box 6)
    - Haanein, Khatab M. (Box 6)
    - Hastings, Cecil, Jr. (Box 6)
    - Hays, William L. (Box 6)
    - Heathcote, C. R. (Box 6)
    - Hege, Vijaya (Box 6)
    - Heller, Walter W. (Box 6)
    - Henry, George E. (Box 6)
    - Herd, G. Ronald (Box 6)
    - Herdan, G. (Box 6)
    - Hess, Seymour (Box 6)
    - Hewett, John E. (Box 6)
    - Hicks, J. S. (Box 6)
    - Hildreth, Clifford (Box 6)
    - Hilgard, E. R., Halsey, A. H., and Savage, I. R. (Box 6)
    - Hill, Bruce M. (Box 6)
    - Hill, Elizabeth J. (Box 6)
    - Hiniker, John Paul (Box 6)
    - Hoadley, A. Bruce (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - Hochdorf, Martin (Box 6)
    - Hodges, Joseph L., Jr. (Box 6)
    - Hoeffding, Wassily (Box 6)
    - Hoffman, Dorothy L. (Box 6)
    - Hogg, Robert V. (Box 6)
    - Holden-Day, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Holford, Theodore (Box 6)
    - Holland, Paul W. (Box 6)
    - Hollander, Myles (Box 6)
    - Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc. (Box 6)
    - Holte, Fritz C. (Box 6)
    - Hooke, Robert, and Belz, Maurice H. (Box 6)
    - Hopkins, B. L. (Box 6)
    - Horvath, William J. (Box 6)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 6)
    - House Document 91-137, U.S. House of Representatives. Committee on Science and Astronautics, Subcommittee on Science, Research, and Development: prepared by Science Policy Research Division (Box 6)
    - Hoyer, Robert (Box 6)
    - Hoyle, B. J., and Baker, G. A. (Box 6)
    - Hoyle, M. H. (Box 6)
    - Hsi, Bartholomew P. (Box 6)
    - Hunt, Hurshell H., and FInley R. D. (Box 6)
    - Hunter, Christopher (Box 6)
    - Hurwicz, Leonid (Box 6)
    - Hutchings, Raymond (Box 6)
    - Huynh, H., and Feldt, Leonard S. (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - I (Box 6)
    - Ifram, Adnan F. (Box 6)
    - Ingham, Roy (Box 6)
    - Institute of Mathematical Statistics
      - Classification (Box 6)
      - Council (Box 6)
      - Index (Box 6)
      - List of Members (Box 6)
      - Nominating Committee (Box 6)
      - Program Committee (Box 6)
      - Visiting Lecturer Committee (Box 6)
    - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences (Box 6)
    - International Statistical Institute (Box 6)
    - International Symposium on Population and Statistics (Box 6)
    - J (Box 6)
    - J (misc.) (Box 7)
    - Jackson, J. Edward, and Morris, Robert H. (Box 7)
    - Jaech, John L. (Box 7)
    - Jain, Vijay K. (Box 7)
    - Janardan, K. G., and Patil, G. P. (Box 7)
    - Jardine, R. (Box 7)
    - Jaspen, Nathan (Box 7)
    - Jasper, Norman H. (Box 7)
    - Jaynes, E. T. (Box 7)
    - Jennrich, Robert I. (Box 7)
    - Jensen, Donald R. (Box 7)
    - Jogdeo, Kumas (Box 7)
    - John, S. (Box 7)
    - John Wiley and Sons, Publishers (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Johns, Vernon (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Gerald W. (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Mark E. (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Roger (Box 7)
    - Johnson, Ronald Kenneth (Box 7)
    - Joiner, Brian L. (Box 7)
    - Joksch, Hans C. (Box 7)
    - Jones, Howard L. (Box 7)
    - Jones, R. D. H., and Hinkelmann, K. (Box 7)
    - Jorgens, Joseph (Box 7)
    - Joshi, Prakash C. (Box 7)
    - Journal of Mathematical Sociology (Box 7)
    - Journal of the American Statistical Association
      - Index (Box 7)
      - Methodology editorship (Box 7)
    - Judge, George G., and Takayama, T. (Box 7)
    - K (Box 7)
    - Kabe, D. G (Box 7)
    - Kadane, Joseph B. (Box 7)
    - Kahn, Paul M. (Box 7)
    - Kaliski, S. F. (Box 7)
    - Kane, Victor (Box 7)
    - Kanofsky, Paul (Box 7)
    - Kao, H. K. (Box 7)
    - Kareken, John H. (Box 7)
    - Karlin, Samuel (Box 7)
    - Karns, F. D. (Box 7)
    - Kase, Shigeo (Box 7)
    - Katti, Shri K. (Box 7)
    - Katz, Leo (Box 7)
    - Kelejian, Harry H. (Box 7)
    - Kelly, Paul (Box 7)
    - Kempthorne, Oscar, and Doerfler, T. E. (Box 7)
    - Kendall, Maurice (Box 7)
    - Keyfitz, Nathan (Box 7)
    - Khatri, C. G. (Box 7)
    - Kiefer, Jack (Box 7)
    - Kimball, Bradford F. (Box 7)
    - Kimeldorf, George (Box 7)
    - Kleijnen, J. C. P., and Naylor, T. H. (Box 7)
    - Klein, Morton, and Rosenberg, L. (Box 7)
    - Klotz, Jerome H. (Box 7)
    - Knight, William (Box 7)
    - Knott, Martin (Box 7)
    - Koerts, John (Box 7)
    - Konijn, Henry S. (Box 7)
    - Koop, John C. (Box 7)
    - Kowalski, Charles J. (Box 7)
    - Korwar, Ramesh (Box 7)
    - Kozelka, Richard L. (Box 7)
    - Kpedekpo, G. M. K. (Box 7)
    - Kraft, Charles, and Van Eeden, Constance (Box 7)
    - Kramer, Gerald H. (Box 7)
    - Krishnaiah, P. R. (Box 7)
    - Krishnaji, N., and Reddy, V. Nagi (Box 7)
    - Krishnaswami, P., and Nath, R. (Box 7)
    - Krumbein, W. C. (Box 7)
    - Kruskal, Joseph (Box 7)
    - Kruskal, William H. (Box 7)
    - Krutchkoff, Richard G. (Box 7)
    - Kuang, H. P. (Box 7)
    - Kuhn, Thomas S. (Box 7)
    - Kullback, S. (Box 7)
    - Kulldorff, Gunnar (Box 7)
    - L (Box 8)
    - Lambert, William W. (Box 8)
    - Lancaster, H. O. (Box 8)
    - Land, Kenneth C. (Box 8)
    - Larson, Lanny D. (Box 8)
    - Lawson, Michael (Box 8)
    - Lawton, Robert O. (Box 8)
    - Lazarsfeld, Paul (Box 8)
    - Leik, Robert K. (Box 8)
    - LeMaster, Vaughn (Box 8)
    - Lemmer, H. H., and Stoker, D. J. (Box 8)
    - LeMoyne Art Foundation, Inc. (Box 8)
    - Lempers, F. B., Harkema, R., and Kloek, T. (Box 8)
    - Leone, Fred C. (Box 8)
    - Levene, Howard (Box 8)
    - Lever, Claudia (Box 8)
    - Lever, William E. (Box 8)
    - Levine, Arnold (Box 8)
    - Levine David L. (Box 8)
    - Leysieffer, Fred (Box 8)
    - Lienert, G. A, and Sarris, V. (Box 8)
    - Lientz, Bennet P. (Box 8)
    - Li, Chou Hsiung (Box 8)
    - Licklider, J. C. R. (Box 8)
    - Lieberman, Gerald J. (Box 8)
    - [Lieblein] (Box 8)
    - Lillifors, H. W. (Box 8)
    - Lin, Pi-Erh (Box 8)
    - Lindgren, Bernard (Box 8)
    - Lindzey, Gardner (Box 8)
    - Likes, Jiri (Box 8)
    - Lipner, Harry (Box 8)
    - Literature Resources in Statistics (Box 8)
    - Locks, Mitchell O. (Box 8)
    - Lohrding, Ronald K. (Box 8)